keepvid.com 2019-12-13

# [OFFICIAL] KeepVid Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

###### 1\. Logging IP Addresses

Our different processes do not require us to know your IP so we do not log and do not collect any IP addresses.

###### 2\. How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

###### 3\. Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

###### 4\. Links to other websites

KeepVid.com may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

###### 5\. Collected Information

KeepVid.com respects the privacy of its users and does not collect any personal information about its users.

###### 6．Third-Party Websites and Services

KeepVid.com may have third-party services, such as Google Analytics, on our website. We don’ty have control of these third-party services, including their information collection and use practices. We are not responsible for their privacy practices or policies. We therefore recommend you to review the privacy policies of these third-party services before providing any personal information to them. For more information about the third-party services which may be included in our website, please contact use at contact@keepvid.com.

Third-party vendors, such as Google, may show ads of KeepVid.com on sites all across the Internet. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads by setting up in [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).
